♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 11=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 11 =
Who is she?
من هي؟
Never seen her before.
لم أرها من قبل.
Some gold-digger who lied her way into here?
بعض المنقبين عن الذهب الذين كذبوا طريقها إلى هنا؟
Oh. Why are you so clumsy?
أوه.  لماذا أنت أخرق جدا؟
It slipped in my hand.
انزلقت في يدي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
لقد فعلت ذلك عن قصد ، أليس كذلك؟
Qin Zhirou.
تشين زيرو.
Why are you sticking up for her?
لماذا تتمسك بها؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Apologize when you did something wrong.
اعتذر عندما فعلت شيئًا خاطئًا.
Or I'll tell Ms. Fu
أو سأخبر السيدة فو
that you were giving her a hard time.
بأنك كنت تمنحها وقتًا عصيبًا.
We'll see who's bringing shame on herself.
سنرى من يجلب العار على نفسها.
She's a big star.
إنها نجمة كبيرة.
Always comes to the poor one's aid.
يأتي دائما لمساعدة الفقراء.
We can't afford to cross her.
لا يمكننا تحمل عبورها.
Let's go then.
لنذهب إذا.
We can't afford to go against her.
لا يمكننا تحمل الذهاب ضدها.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
The stain is everywhere.
البقعة في كل مكان.
I'll take you to clean it up.
سآخذك لتنظيفه.
Yeah.
نعم.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
I can't get rid of the stain.
لا أستطيع التخلص من البقعة.
You are Qin Zhirou, right?
أنت تشين زيرو ، أليس كذلك؟
I really like your TV show.
أنا حقا أحب برنامجك التلفزيوني.
Xiangxiang, you are too courteous.
شيانغشيانغ ، أنت مهذب للغاية.
Just call me Zhirou.
فقط اتصل بي زيرو.
I've known Si...
لقد عرفت سي ...
Well, Fu Sihan, Mr. Fu.
حسنًا ، فو سيهان ، السيد فو.
I know him very well.
انا اعرفه جيدا
Just tell me if you need any help in the future.
فقط أخبرني إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي مساعدة في المستقبل.
Thank you. You are so nice.
شكرًا لك.  انت لطيف جدا.
The party is beginning soon.
الحفلة ستبدأ قريبا
You can't go out like this.
لا يمكنك الخروج هكذا.
Oh, I know. Wait a second.
اه انا اعرف.  انتظر لحظة.
Take it off.
انزعها.
Okay.
تمام.
I used this shawl
لقد استخدمت هذا الشال
when I was on set in France.
عندما كنت في فرنسا.
You can use it for today.
يمكنك استخدامه لهذا اليوم.
(I am stupid) It's so pretty.
(أنا غبي) إنها جميلة جدًا.
Mr. Fu, I need you to sign this.
السيد فو ، أريدك أن توقع هذا.
You are not thinking about Miss Yun, are you?
أنت لا تفكر في الآنسة يون ، أليس كذلك؟
Can she manage it on her own?
هل تستطيع إدارتها بنفسها؟
She...
هي...
Chu He.
تشو هي.
Forget about your bonus this month.
نسيان مكافأتك هذا الشهر.
Boss.
رئيس.
Did I hit a nerve or something?
هل أصبت بالعصب أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
I'm worried that she'll make us look bad.
أنا قلق من أنها ستجعلنا نبدو سيئين.
Fu Rong won't make it easy for her.
لن تجعل فو رونغ الأمر سهلاً عليها.
Are we going there to save her?
هل نحن ذاهبون إلى هناك لإنقاذها؟
You are here.
أنت هنا.
That woman is so stupid.
تلك المرأة غبية جدا.
What does Fu Sihan see in her?
ماذا ترى فو سيهان فيها؟
Who knows?
من تعرف؟
But we make fun of her like this.
لكننا نسخر منها هكذا.
What if her family comes looking for trouble?
ماذا لو أتت عائلتها بحثًا عن المتاعب؟
What do we do then?
ماذا سنفعل إذن؟
Don't worry. As far as I know,
لا تقلق.  بقدر ما أعرف،
the Yun family lives in Quebec, Canada.
تعيش عائلة يون في كيبيك ، كندا.
The people speak French over there.
الناس يتحدثون الفرنسية هناك.
But that woman
لكن تلك المرأة
can't even realize that the words on the shawl
لا أستطيع حتى أن أدرك أن الكلمات على الشال
is an insult.
إهانة.
She must be an imposter.
يجب أن تكون دجال.
Then we have to give her a good lesson.
ثم علينا أن نعطيها درسًا جيدًا.
Thank you for attending this party today, ladies.
شكرا لك على حضور هذه الحفلة اليوم ، سيداتي.
Today, I'll introduce you someone special.
اليوم ، سأقدم لك شخصًا مميزًا.
The daughter of the Yun Group,
ابنة مجموعة يون ،
Yun Xiangxiang.
يون شيانغشيانغ.
(Thankfully, when I was gathering information before,)
(لحسن الحظ ، عندما كنت أجمع المعلومات من قبل ،)
(I specially looked into the details of Fu Sihan's private life.)
(لقد بحثت بشكل خاص في تفاصيل حياة فو سيهان الخاصة.)
(Qin Zhirou.)
(تشين زيرو).
(She has been courting Fu Sihan for years.)
(لقد كانت تغازل فو سيهان لسنوات).
(I didn't even introduce myself back there,)
(لم أقم بتقديم نفسي مرة أخرى هناك ،)
(and she called me Miss Yun.)
(ودعتني الآنسة يون.)
(She knew who I am,)
(عرفت من أنا)
(and told me intentionally that she knows Fu Sihan well.)
(وأخبرتني عمدًا أنها تعرف فو سيهان جيدًا.)
(This is the classic female villain.)
(هذه هي الشرير الأنثوي الكلاسيكي).
(So easy to tackle.)
(من السهل جدًا معالجته).